(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-03T02:19:14.344932",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
バンダイ、バンプレスピリッツより
From Bandai and Banpresto spirits,
ホロライブEXPO 2025の会場にある特設ブースで展示中の商品をご紹介！
introducing items available at the special booth during hololive EXPO 2025!
ここで展示中の商品をご紹介！
Check out all the wonderful merchandise on display!
ホロライブEXPO 2025限定の一番くじ特設フォトブースも展開中！
And the Ichiban Kuji special photo booth for hololive EXPO 2025 is also open!
モニターをタッチしてくじ運をめくり、
Touch the monitor to flip through fortune slips,
出てきたデザインと一緒に撮影できます！
and you can take a picture with the design that appears!
hololive 5th fes.
で歌われた名曲
Songs performed at
The Last Frontier
フィギュア化決定！
are now getting scale figures!
あの感動をもう一度…
Relive that emotion once more...
スケールフィギュア化決定！
Scale figures announced!
パペットぬいぐるみ
Puppet Plushies
寝そべりぬいぐるみ
Sleeping Plushies
指パペット
Finger Puppets
キャンディ缶
Candy Tins
ひっかけフィギュアも登場！
Hikkake Figures coming in April!
台湾旅行中、最も便利な決済サービスを提供します。
Providing the most convenient payment service during your trip to Taiwan.
新商品まもなく登場！
New products coming soon!
hololive 6th fes. 一卡通限定盲包 第一弾 全20+1種
hololive 6th fes. iPASS Limited Blind Box Vol. 1 (20 + 1 types)
2025年夏 発売予定
Releasing Summer 2025
hololive 6th fes. 一卡通限定盲包 第二弾 全20+1種
hololive 6th fes. iPASS Limited Blind Box Vol. 2 (20 + 1 types)
2025年夏 発売予定
Releasing Summer 2025
hololive 6th fes. 一卡通限定盲包 第三弾 全20+1種
hololive 6th fes. iPASS Limited Blind Box Vol. 3 (20 + 1 types)
2025年夏 発売予定
Releasing Summer 2025
歌いたい曲が入っていなかった
Could not find the song you wanted to sing?
JOYSOUND X1で歌おうぜ！
Sing it out with JOYSOUND X1!
KARAOKE 最高！
Karaoke at its absolute best!
JOYSOUND X1でボリュームしよう！ JOYSOUND X1
Having songs you want to sing is the best with JOYSOUND X1!
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention for visitors
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights
during the performance.
声出し応援 OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Please be aware of flashing lights
during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
バンダイ・バンダイスピリッツより
From Bandai and Bandai Spirits,
ホロライブエキスポ2025の会場にある特設ブースで展示中の商品をご紹介！
introducing products on display at the special booth at hololive EXPO 2025!
ホロライブエキスポ2025限定の一番くじ特設フォトブースも展開中！
Also featuring a special hololive EXPO 2025 limited Ichibankuji photo booth!
モニターをタッチしてクジ券をめくり、出てきたデザインと一緒に撮影できます！
Touch the monitor to draw a lottery ticket and take a photo with the resulting design!
未知の期待 抱え 出会った
Holding expectations of the unknown, we met
あの日の僕らは 底に湧き上がる 何かを 言葉にできなくて
on that day, we couldn't put into words
フィギュア化決定！
Figure release decided!
あの感動をもう一度... 旅立つ歌を
That emotion once more... A song to set off.
スケールフィギュア化決定！
Scale figure release decided!
フリューから「ホロライブ」プライズが
Hololive prizes from FuRyu
全国アミューズメント施設にて続々展開中！
now rolling out in amusement facilities nationwide!
4月からは新たにひっかけフィギュアも登場！
Starting in April, hanging figures will also appear!
台湾旅行中、最も便利な決済サービスを提供します。
Providing the most convenient payment service during your trip to Taiwan.
歌いたい曲が入っていなかった
The song you wanted to sing wasn't there
だったらJOYSOUND X1で歌おうぜ！
Then let's sing on JOYSOUND X1!
JOYSOUND X1 オンデマンド！
JOYSOUND X1 On Demand!
JOYSOUND X1 曲数No.1！
JOYSOUND X1 #1 in song count!
AIが採点 絶賛
AI scoring and praise
KARAOKE 最高
KARAOKE Supreme
曲数No.1 歌いたい曲があるって最高！
#1 in song count, having songs you want to sing is the best!
超特大ぬいぐるみブランド どきゅーと から商品化決定！
Commercialization decided from the ultra-large plush brand Dokuqute!
約100cmサイズぬいぐるみ に！
As an approx. 100cm sized plush!
2025年夏 受注開始予定
Scheduled to start accepting orders in Summer 2025
タイトーブースにてサンプル展示中！
Samples on display at the Taito booth!
グルーブコースター最新作に白上フブキと
In the latest Groove Coaster with Shirakami Fubuki and
さくらみこがキャラクターボイスで参戦！
Sakura Miko joining with character voices!
人気曲や、私たちが歌う曲も楽しめる！
Enjoy popular songs and songs sung by us too!
私たちがグルーヴワールドをナビゲートするよ！
We will navigate the Groove World!
誰よりもっと夢を追いかけたい
Want to chase dreams more than anyone
ワクワクと止まらない 想像を超えてく
Unstoppable excitement, going beyond imagination
世界にしてあげる
I'll make it the world
コラボイベント実施中！
Collaboration event ongoing!
ゲームのオアシスに飛び込め！
Jump into the gaming oasis!
PalVerse フィギュア化決定！！
PalVerse Figure release decided!!
白上フブキ・大神ミオ フィギュア化決定 3月8日(土)予約開始！！
Shirakami Fubuki & Ookami Mio Figure release decided! Pre-orders start March 8th!
宝鐘マリン 1/7スケールフィギュア 締切間近
Houshou Marine 1/7 scale figure deadline approaching
SHIBUYA TSUTAYA 書店 × Design COCO 新ブランド始動
SHIBUYA TSUTAYA Bookstore x Design COCO New Brand Launch
推しの夢 叶えます。
Making your oshi's dream come true.
2025年夏 コラボカフェ・プライズ 開催決定！
Summer 2025 Collab Cafe & Prize Event Decided!
続報は公式XやHPをチェック！
Check official X and website for updates!
harmony 重ねた言葉 届け
harmony — layered words, reach out
たどたどしく 描いては
clumsily drawing our dreams
ぎこちない と笑っていた
laughing at how awkward they seemed
未来予想 あの日の続きを見よう
let’s continue the story we envisioned that day
手と手繋いで 風も着こなして
hand in hand, embracing the wind
扉を叩いて 連れていってよ
knocking on doors — we’ll go together
どんなことも きっと
no matter what comes our way
一緒なら 叶えていける
if we’re together, we can make it happen
ララララ
La la la la
鳴りやまない 希望のベル ほら
The bell of hope keeps ringing — listen
ララララ
La la la la
聞こえてる歌 ah
Can you hear this song? Ah...
harmony 重ねた言葉
harmony — layered words
鮮やかな 日々の向こうへ
Beyond the vivid days ahead
ずっと君と 彩るストーリー
Always with you, we’ll color this story
ハートに結んだ 夢が
The dreams tied to our hearts
空へかけてゆく
Race toward the sky
キラメキに乗せて あなたへ届け
Carried on shimmering light — let them reach you
メロディーどこまでも
This melody — endlessly!
何気ないこと 思い出す
Recalling the little things
一人じゃないよって深呼吸
Taking a deep breath, knowing I’m not alone
未体験楽しむ 魔法の言葉
Embracing the unknown — that’s the magic of words
一息ついて ふと振り返って
Pausing for a moment, looking back
また君を知って そのたびに
Learning more about you each time
ちょっと勇気出して
And with just a bit of courage
明日へ飛び込んでいける
I can dive into tomorrow
ララララ
La la la la
降り積もる 道しるべは まだ
The path ahead is still being laid
ララララ
La la la la
覚えてる歌 ah
Yet I remember this song, ah...
harmony 手を伸ばしたら
harmony — when I reach out
足跡に虹がかかる
A rainbow forms over our footprints
きっと晴れる 口ずさむステージ
The sky will surely clear, humming on this stage
ハートに記した 場所へ
Guided by the marks on my heart
運ぶ約束を
A promise carries me forward
輝きに乗せて
Riding on its radiance
世界へ響け
Let it echo through the world
メロディーいつまでも
This melody, forever!
ララララ 君と踏み出した あの一歩 あの瞬間が
La la la la — that first step we took together, that moment
ララララ 宝物だって 胸を張る今
La la la la — is now a treasure I hold with pride
ララララ 歩いて話して はしゃいで笑顔でゆくんだ
La la la la — walking, talking, smiling, moving forward
ララララ 色褪せないまま
La la la la — without fading away
ララララ 混ざり合う 僕らの声 ほら
La la la la — our voices blend together — listen
ララララ 聞こえてる歌 ah
La la la la — can you hear this song? Ah...
harmony 重ねた言葉
harmony — layered words
鮮やかな 日々の向こうへ
Beyond the vivid days ahead
ずっと君と 彩るよストーリー
Always with you, we’ll color this story
ハートに結んだ夢が
The dreams tied to our hearts
空へかけてゆく
Race toward the sky
キラメキに乗せて あなたへ届け
Carried on shimmering light — let them reach you
世界へ響け 愛を込めて
Let them echo through the world with love
メロディーどこまでも
This melody — endlessly!
harmony 重ねた言葉 届け
harmony — layered words, reach out
たどたどしく 描いて は
clumsily drawing our dreams
ぎこちない と 笑っ て た
laughing at how awkward they seemed
未来 予想 あの日 の 続き を 見 よう
let’s continue the story we envisioned that day
手と手 繋い で 風 も 着こなして
hand in hand, embracing the wind
扉 叩い て 連れ て く おー
knock on doors — we’ll go together
どんな こと も きっと
no matter what comes our way
一緒 なら 叶え て いける
if we’re together, we can make it happen
【 la - la - la - la 】
[ la - la - la - la ]
鳴りやま ない 希望 の ベル ほら
the bell of hope keeps ringing — listen
【 la - la - la - la 】
[ la - la - la - la ]
聴こえ て いる 歌 ah
can you hear this song? ah…
harmony 重ね た 言葉
harmony — layered words
鮮やか な 日々 の 向こうえ
beyond the vivid days ahead
ずっと 君 と 彩る よ ストーリー
always with you, we’ll color this story
ハート に 結ん だ 夢 が
the dreams tied to our hearts
空 へ 駆け て ゆく
race toward the sky
キラメキ に 乗せ て
carried on shimmering light —
あなたへ 届け
let them reach you
メロディー どこまでも ！
this melody — endlessly!
Welcome！ あなたは選ばれし ポルカサーカス初めてのお客様！
Welcome! You are the chosen guest of Polka Circus!
やあやあお待たせしました とてもハッピーな動物たち
Welcome back, sorry to keep you waiting!
ユカイでかわいい 魔界の子からエルフまで
From magical creatures to elves!
TV Showじゃない ここだけのサーカス
Not a TV show, a circus just for here!
It's show time！！
It's show time!!
なにがみたい？ どんなことでもしてあげる
What would you like to see? I can do anything for you!
私は座長その名も尾丸ポルカ
I'm the ringmaster, Omaru Polka!
ぜったい笑顔にさせちゃうぜスマイル！
I'll definitely make you smile!
それでは最後まで付き合ってもらうからな！
So let's stick together till the very end!
準備は出来てますか Are you ready？
Are you ready?
さあさあ近くにおいてきっと誰しもが仰天
Come closer and everyone will look up in awe!
奇想天外なショーの始まりさ
The start of a fantastic, out-of-this-world show!
グッと惹かれるでしょ？ おっと！押さないでね
You're hooked, right? Whoops, don't rush!
それでは準備okですか？
So, is everything ready?
愉しみな動物たち 玉乗りピエロ
Pleasant animals, ball-balancing clowns!
ハラハラドキドキしちゃうでしょ？
It'll make your heart race, won't it?
真っ赤な輪くぐろう 綱渡りしてて
Walking the tightrope over a bright red ring!
ちょっとくらいのドジなんてご愛敬よ
A little bit of daring is just for your entertainment!
Come on！ light up！
Come on! Light up!
とっておきのライブボートとしてないで もっと！
As the ultimate live broadcast, don't stop now, more!
さあもっと！ 手を叩こう！
Come on, even more! Let's clap our hands!
ほらほらついておいでいて目も回るようなサーカス
Hey, keep up, it's a circus that'll make your head spin!
きっとここだけだよ
Surely, only right here!
ホログラムみたいキラキラ奇跡が踊る
Shimmering miracles like a hologram dance!
いつかは世界中を虜にしちゃうぞ
Soon we're gonna make the whole world our own!
う～ん明日の演目はどうしようかな
Hmm, what should tomorrow's program be?
屋根裏で秘密の作戦会議さ
A secret strategy meeting behind the scenes!
いっぱいのお客席がアッと言驚くような
A thrilling show that'll leave the packed audience amazed!
とびきりのショーを見せましょう
Let's put on an exceptional show!
思い付いたらジッとしてられない
Whenever I think of something, I just can't sit still!
座員を引っ張ってきてLet's go！
Bringing the crew along, let's go!
ねえあれがやりたい！ これもやりたい！
"Hey, I wanna do that!" "I wanna do this too!"
どうして時間って足りないの？
Why is there never enough time?
上手くいかなくて空回ってばかりで
Sometimes things don't go well and I'm just spinning my wheels,
少し落ち込んでしまう日もあるけれど見ててね
and on days when I feel a little down, but look,
大丈夫！ いつまでもクヨクヨしてらんないし
It's okay! We won't stay down forever,
顔を上げて今日のステージがほらね！待ってるのさ
So raise your head, today's stage is—wait for it!
ポルカおるか？ ポルカおるんか？
Polka is here? Polka is all here?
ポルカおるか？ ポルカ歌うか♪
Polka is here? Polka will sing!♪
ポルカおるか？ ポルカ終わるか？
Polka is here? Is Polka finished?
ポルカおるか？ ポルカ踊るか♪
Polka is here? Polka will dance!♪
強く強く願うんだどんな夢だってきっとそうきっと叶うはず
Strongly, strongly wishing, no matter what dream it is, it'll surely come true!
何も怖くないみんなの日々は全部ちゃんと届いているよ
Nothing to fear, everyday is reaching everyone properly!
さあ新しい次元新しい舞台へ
Now, to a new dimension, a new stage,
もっと！さあもっと！突き進もう！
More! Come on, more! Let's push forward!
That’s good game, what a shame.
That's good game, what a shame.
Players, they all complain
"Why me?" "No not again!"
Shout! Ratatata~ but!
Ain't got time so dry those eyes
Look around what’s that I spy
The broken and bruised
All got something to prove now
Abracadabra let’s go
Watch them like dice as they fall
Double one, double win
Lowly to lottery
Do or die We hit that high
Snake eyes, snake eyes
Here we go again, a brand-new day
My morning coffee, so perfect I can't complain
Ready, steady, race
Hang tight on the reins
It’s time to have some fun
It’s the perfect frame, I’m feeling great
Making my way, enjoying the view
Feel the gentle breeze with every step I take
Like it’s calling out my name
Life is the wildest ride!
Emerald City, I’ll find my brick road
Ready, steady, race
Hang tight on the reins
And let’s just have some fun
It’s the perfect frame, I’m feeling great
Making my way, enjoying the view
Feel the gentle breeze with every step I take
Like it’s calling out my name
Life is the wildest ride!
Can you feel the sunshine hitting just right?
All day, we play, no regrets
Place my bet, just let the chips fall
If it rains on me, I’ll just roll up sleeves
We only do what we can do
Some days, we’ll rest and just hit snooze
With a pocket full of dreams, we can touch the sky
Ready, steady, race
Hang tight on the reins
And let’s just have some fun
It’s the perfect frame, I’m feeling great
Making my way, enjoying the view
(La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la)
Feel the gentle breeze with every step I take
Like it’s calling out my name
Life is the wildest ride!
Come on, everyone!
Give it up for the show!
(La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la)
Skies looking clear, and I know I’m make it there
Emerald City, I’ll find my brick road
Ready, steady, race
Hang tight on the reins
Look at me now, hit with a pulse of a heartbeat leaping heart-crying, reckless girl
A crazy show, reckless show
Anytime, anywhere, we're talking about global-scale runaway thrills
Feel the joy of the world opening up
Shouting out loud, shouting out loud
Even if we stumble over words before we can speak
We keep searching for the juice of youth, dancing carelessly day and night
Calling out loud, shouting out loud
(No escape!)
Bursting with emotions, driven by impulse
Even if we're stopped, we can't stop anymore
Surrendering to impulse, heading into a daybreak
Hang on tightly now!
(Nah, nah, nah, nah, ready for my show)
Even if we get scolded, we don't care how we live our lives
(Rock 'n' roll!)
Even if we play idly, we're talking about global-scale runaway thrills
Shouting out loud, shouting out loud
To cause a miracle, stay with me
Whatever you want, don't forget to shout out
Shouting out loud, shouting out loud
Gather them all up to the right and left
Can you hear it, can you hear it?
What are you going to do about this detour? Shouting out loud, shouting out loud
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah!
Left behind at the end of a long, distant journey
The mountain of gold where the unidentified bell rings
What his presence brings is unending greed
Instead of being fed up, I pretend not to notice while living my life
Turning the tables right in front of the mirror
Passing through the masked masked masquerade
Tonight, people go wild, dancing and dancing away
The chest where the stray cat's heart leaps out
Unraveling the deep mystery of the flower garden
Shine as fast as lightning!
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, yobai!
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, the bell tolls for a grand shift!
Climbing up to the top of the throne of gold!
Dance, dance, dance, come on, let's dance!
Breathe out your intense sorrow!
漠然とした不安 欲しがっていたfun
Vague anxiety, fun I wanted,
日常に違和感？ うんざりしていた
feeling uncomfortable in everyday life? I was tired.
見慣れたありきたりな眺め
A familiar and common view,
理屈を超える変化を求めていた
I was looking for a change that exceeded theory.
窮屈で退屈な日々の中
In the cramped and boring days,
突然キミは現れた
you suddenly appeared.
全身の細胞駆け巡るように
As if running through all my cells,
走り出した未完成なストーリー
an unfinished story began to run.
モノクロだった景色が今
The scenery that was monochrome is now
キミと出会いカラフルに彩る brand new world
colorful and brand new when meeting you.
ココロ奪われた
My heart was stolen.
気まぐれな 瞬間 ハートビート
A whimsical, fleeting heartbeat,
揺らぐ時空の狭間
swaying in the space-time gap.
もう ひとりじゃない 煌めく星
I am no longer alone, a sparkling star.
描く未来予想図は
The future forecast diagram we draw
同じ夢を引き寄せたいよ
wants to draw the same dream closer.
果てしない旅路の向こうで
Beyond the endless journey,
鳴りやまないロマンが待っている
an endless romance is waiting.
気づいたときにはね i can't live without you
When I realized, I couldn't live without you.
いつでもキミと一緒になら
Whenever I am together with you,
ここから先広がる宇宙
the universe spreads out from here.
晴れ渡る空飛び出して
Jumping out into the sunny sky,
気分は上々 想像以上
my spirits are higher than imagined.
机上の空論は終わりにして
Leaving desktop theories behind,
すべて叶える絵空事
making all fantasies come true.
時計の針が回り回り
The clock's hands spin and spin
限られた時の中で
within limited time,
鮮やかに出 dancing time
a vivid dancing time begins.
ココロ奪われた
My heart was stolen.
気まぐれな 瞬間 ハートビート
A whimsical, fleeting heartbeat,
揺らぐ時空の狭間
swaying in the space-time gap.
もう ひとりじゃない 煌めく星
I am no longer alone, a sparkling star.
描く未来予想図は
The future forecast diagram we draw
同じ夢を引き寄せたいよ
wants to draw the same dream closer.
果てしない旅路の向こうで
Beyond the endless journey,
紛れもない奇跡があるはずさ
there must be an unmistakable miracle.
さよなら メランコリック
Goodbye, melancholic.
止められはしない この衝動
This urge cannot be stopped.
突き進むだけさ 形振りかまわず are you ready?
Just push forward without caring, are you ready?
限界はないさ 度度無限大の異次元
There are no limits, an infinite dimension.
散りばめられた閃き 夜空満ちていく
Scattered flashes fill the night sky.
喜びは哀しみの倍分 分かち合っていこう
Let's double the joy and sorrow together.
キミとなら どこまでも
With you, anywhere.
疲れたときには戻って おいでよ
When you're tired, come back.
バイバイ 仮面は舞踏会
Bye-bye, masks at the masquerade.
今夜も羽ばたけよ
Spread your wings tonight as well.
狂気と欲望の夜 駆け上がれ
Soar through the night of madness and desire.
ほら ほら 踊れよ 三本万歳 恋のシャバダバ
Come on, dance, three cheers for love's shabadaba!
三々五々 恋車は 刹那の追い競よ
Scattered carriages of love chasing in the fleeting moments.
瞬間クライマックス
Momentary climax.
狂気よ 忘れて更ける ダンスフロア
Let madness fade on the dancing floor.
バイバイ 仮面は舞踏会
Bye-bye, masks at the masquerade.
今夜も羽ばたけよ
Spread your wings tonight as well.
狂気と欲望の夜 駆け上がれ
Soar through the night of madness and desire.
バイバイ 仮面は舞踏会
Bye-bye, masks at the masquerade.
音乃瀬奏
Otonose Kanade
一条莉々華
Ichijou Ririka
儒烏風亭らでん
Juufuutei Raden
轟はじめ
Todoroki Hajime
火威青
Hiodoshi Ao & ReGLOSS
漠然とした不安 欲しがっていたfun
Vague anxiety, fun I wanted,
見慣れたありきたりな眺め 理屈を超える変化を求めていた
A familiar and common view, searching for changes beyond theory.
窮屈で退屈な日々の中 突然キミは現れた
In cramped and boring days, you suddenly appeared.
全身の細胞駆け巡るように 走り出した未完成なストーリー
Running like cells coursing through the body, an unfinished story.
モノクロだった景色が今 キミと出会いカラフルに彩る brand new world
Monochrome scenery is now colored brand new when meeting you.
ココロ奪われた 気まぐれな 瞬間 ハートビート
My heart was stolen by a whimsical, fleeting heartbeat.
揺らぐ時空の狭間 もう ひとりじゃない 煌めく星
Swaying in space-time, I am no longer alone, a sparkling star.
描く未来予想図は 同じ夢を引き寄せたいよ
The future forecast we draw wants to pull the same dream close.
果てしない旅路の向こうで 鳴りやまないロマンが待っている
Beyond the endless journey, an endless romance awaits.
紐解いた新章
Unraveling a new chapter,
様変わりしていく show time
a changing show time.
全然悪くないイマジネーション
It's a completely fine imagination.
視界の霧は晴れ渡って
The fog in my vision clears away,
悲しみに別れを告げる
bidding farewell to sadness.
酸いも甘いも宙に放り出して
Tossing both the sweet and sour into the sky,
滲む空インクは薔薇色
the bleeding ink of the sky is rose-colored.
飛び出せ to the future
Jump out to the future,
フライングしたって alright
even if we fly early, it's alright.
restart line!!
ときめいてしまえば
Once it sets your heart aflutter,
瞬く間に広がる開放区
an open zone spreads in the blink of an eye.
一つ一つすべてがドラマ
Every single thing is a drama.
待ちわびた daybreak
The long-awaited daybreak,
restart line!!
代わる代わる彩るパノラマ
A changing, colorful panorama,
満ち溢れるフィーリングラデーション
overflowing feeling-radation,
始まりのその時が来た
the moment of beginning has arrived.
nothing is impossible
昔こましゃくれた世界
A world that used to be precocious,
この先はまだ誰も知らない正解
the correct answer ahead is still unknown to anyone.
傍観してるだけじゃ味気ない
Just standing by as a spectator is dull.
リアルタイムで通じ合って
Connecting in real-time,
振り子にかけるエモーション
emotions hanging on a pendulum.
後ろ髪引かれても I don't mind
Even if we're held back, I don't mind.
大胆不敵なシチュエーション
A bold and fearless situation,
行けるところまで行ってみたいうえ
I want to go as far as we can go.
選択肢にない get off on the way
Get off on the way with no other choice.
共々に声を鳴らし
Resounding our voices together,
素肌を貫くような
even with the piercing pain
真っ直ぐな痛みが伴っても
running straight through our skin,
この仲間たちと最果てまで keep running to the end
we'll keep running to the end with these companions.
飛び出せ to the future
Jump out to the future,
フライングしたって alright
even if we fly early, it's alright.
restart line!!
ときめいてしまえば
Once it sets your heart aflutter,
瞬く間に広がる開放区
an open zone spreads in the blink of an eye.
一つ一つすべてがドラマ
Every single thing is a drama.
待ちわびた daybreak
The long-awaited daybreak,
restart line!!
代わる代わる彩るパノラマ
A changing, colorful panorama,
満ち溢れるフィーリングラデーション
overflowing feeling-radation,
飛び出せ you raise me up
Jump out, you raise me up,
恐れるものは何もない restart line!!
there is nothing to fear, restart line!!
綺麗なお城だけが
Only a beautiful castle
透明な足跡を照らすよ
illuminates transparent footprints.
restart line!!
ぱり ぴっぷ ぺぺ ぽぴっぽー ぱり ぺり ぷっぴー
Pari pippu pepe popippo pari peri puppy!
空は飛べないけれど
Though we can't fly in the sky,
夢のツバサがある
we have wings of dreams.
だからポタポタ焼き汗流して
So let's sweat it out, dropping by drop,
パクパク大きく育てて
and grow big and strong, bite by bite,
いつか大空を制するのだ！
until we conquer the open sky one day!
自己紹介始まるけれど
Our self-introductions are about to begin, but...
皆さん！へい、こんにちはー！
"Everyone! Hey, hello there!"
どうも、キャッチコピーは
"Well, our catchphrase is:"
体力50キロカロリー！
"Physical strength: 50 kilocalories!"
げきやば！英語潰す天使だ！ハロラミおキツネこのじゃんこたまるからだです！
"Super dangerous! An English-crushing angel! Harurami, the fox Kono, Janko, Tamaru Karada!"
蹴散らすよ！ぽぽぽ！
"We'll scatter them! Popopo!"
そして！ぽぽぽぽぽぽぽ！
"And then! Popopopopopo!"
ちょっと皆さん、今ポルちゃんが自分の名前が分かんなくなってるんだけど
"Hey everyone, Pol-chan doesn't even know her own name right now!"
こういうのやってくれる？ぽぽ？
"Will you do something like this? Popo?"
3文字でこの子の名前を教えてあげられますか？
"Can you tell us this girl's name in 3 letters?"
じゃあ僕「せーの」って言うからみんなお願いしますね！この子の名前は、せーの！
"Then I'll count to three, so everyone please! This girl's name is... Ready, go!"
ぽるかー！
"Polka!"
おーい！からきた！やばいお前ぽるたんだね！みんな楽しんでるかー！
"Hey! It came from! Oh no, you're Poltan! Is everyone having fun?!"
イェーイ！イェーイ！イェーイ！盛り上がってるかー！
"Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Are you getting pumped up?!"
最高！
"The best!"
というわけでうちだレグロスです。
"So anyway, we are ReGLOSS."
違うだろ！
"That's wrong!"
やめてくださいそんな全く台本にないこと。
"Stop it with things completely not in the script!"
いやめっ茶良かったここまで。やっとにね。あっちやっち最初にねポルカのポから始まった時どうしようかと
"No, it was super great up to here. Finally. That first part starting from Polka's 'Po', we were wondering what to do!"
やった！どうでした？やったよ！
"We did it! How was it? We did it!"
凄く良かったも！テンション爆上がりだよ、ここで！
It was so amazing! My excitement is through the roof right here!
あの、ありがとう、みんな！みんなー！
Um, thank you, everyone! Everyoneee!
最高！
Amazing!
ですね！もう超よかったね！
Right! It was already super great!
いや良かったもう！
Man, it was so good!
VERZのもう最高だったなー！
VERZ's performance was just the best!
かなー！本当に、かっこよかったね！めちゃマジで！
Right?! Seriously, it was so cool! Like, for real!
そしてね、船長がね、ええしちゃったね！
And then, Marine did, um...
バイバイしちゃいましたよ！
She said bye-bye!
しましたね！
She did!
出しちゃったね！
She let it out!
よかったねみんな！よかった！
That was great, everyone! So good!
そしてリグロスも最高だったねマジで！
And ReGLOSS was also the best, seriously!
いや本当に！
Yeah, really!
テンション超上がるわ！あーみんなー！
My tension is skyrocketing! Ah, everyoneー!
配信もどう！盛り上がってる？盛り上がってるわ！
How's the stream doing? Are you hyped? It's so hyped!
配信のみんな見てるかー！見てるかー！
Everyone watching the stream, are you watching?! Are you watching?!
よかった！かっこよかったって言ってます！はい、かっこよかったと言っていまして。
Awesome! They're saying it was cool! Yes, they said it was cool.
というわけで、うちらのも、うちらのもかっこいいよな？かっこいいよね！
So, you know, our performance is cool too, right? It's cool, right?
イェーイ！
Yay!
どうですか？
How is it?
どうですか？可愛い可愛い！スカートなんだねそれ！
How is it? So cute! That's a skirt!
まあね。あれ可愛い！
Well, yeah. That's cute!
めっちゃセクシーじゃん。あれみんな、あ、ペンライトきれいだね！
It's super sexy. Look everyone, ah, the penlights are so pretty!
ありがとう！やばい綺麗！ありがとうね！
Thank you! So pretty! Thank you so much!
嬉しい！一応ウェーブでもやっときますか。
I'm so happy! Shall we do a wave just in case?
え、やろっか！じゃあこっちに行くか。
Oh, let's do it! Then let's go this way.
こっちか！で、できるかな？
This way! Can we do it?
ヒーローをね、こうわあってするやつね。ワーツするやつね。こっちからやったらわあってだからね。
You know, that thing where heroes go 'whoosh' like this. If we start from this side, it goes 'whoosh!'.
わかったか？いけるか？フィーリングレッスんでいこう。なんとなく！
Got it? Can you do it? Let's go by feeling. Somehow!
せーの、うわー！
Ready, go, whoa!
戻る！戻るこれ！戻れ！戻れ！戻れ！戻れ！すご！
Go back! Go back! Go back! Go back! Go back! So cool!
ありがとう！ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you!
めっちゃ楽しい！幸せ！幸せ？もうずっと
So much fun! Happiness! Happiness? Forever
あと1時間とか喋りますか？
Shall we chat for another hour or so?
はい、じゃあというわけで、やめる、嘘です、嘘です！
Yes, so then, let's stop—just kidding, just kidding!
すいません。
Sorry.
ライヤーライヤー？ライヤーライヤーだよ！
Liar liar? It's liar liar!
なんて言っておりますけどね、このとても多分緊張してると思いますんで、奏さんも。
That's what we're saying, but I'm sure Kanata-san is super nervous right now too.
もう、緊張しますよお！
I'm so nervous!
誰だかわかんないんですけどね、皆さん！かなたって叫んでください、かなたって！
I don't know who it is, but everyone! Shout 'Kanata!', shout 'Kanata!'
かなたって！
Kanata!
かなたー！
Kanataaa!
やったー！よかったね！嬉しい！
Yay! That's great! I'm so happy!
嬉しい！これはめちゃくちゃ嬉しい！ありがとう！
Happy! This is insanely happy! Thank you!
これからもさ、いろんな節目がここで喋ると思うから、その時もいっぱいペンライト振って応援してあげてね。
From now on too, there will be various milestones where we talk here, so please wave your penlights and cheer us on then as well.
もうぜひ応援してくださいね！緊張して大変なことになってるメンバーもいますから！大変なことに、あー確かに。
Please definitely support them! There are so many members who are super nervous and having a hard time! Having a hard time—ah, true.
逆立ちとかね、ガチラッシュでね、もう痛い気がする。いいないいな！さすが生じませ。
Handstands and all, and with gachi-rush, it sounds painful. Good for you! Not really, though.
はい、というわけでね、あ、これ、あれじゃない？読んで読んで！
Yes, so, hey, isn't this... Read it, read it!
ハッシュタグ！かなた！
Hashtag! Kanata!
ハッシュタグ！#ホロライブフェスEXPO25_DAY1で感想をね、SNSにいっぱいポストしてくださいね終わったらっぱい！
Hashtag! Please post lots of your impressions on SNS with #HololiveFesEXPO25_DAY1 when it's over!
あの、あのネットで見てるお前らもな！よろしく！見てるぞ！
And you guys watching online too! Best regards! We're watching you!
あとね、みにいくからな！そうだよ、みにいくからね！本当にいくんだからな！
Also, we're going to go see you! That's right, we're going to go see you! We're really going!
ずっとトレンド入りさせてくれよな！そうだね！よろしくね！
Keep us trending! That's right! Please do!
そしてここにいるみんなが盛り上げてくれるまま、もっともっとトレンドが乗っていくはず！わあ！
And with everyone here hyping us up, the trends are bound to go even higher! Whoa!
一緒にステージ作り上げていこうぜ！
Let's build this stage together!
そして配信の皆様にお知らせがあります！タター！イエーイ！無料パートは
And we have an announcement for everyone watching the stream! Tada! Yay! The free part is
ここまでです！
ending here!
もういいかい？ここまでで！
Are you done already? Up to here!
早すぎるって！
That's way too fast!
早すぎる！
Too fast!
わかる！もっとやってほしいよね！
I know! We want you to do more!
でもでもでもでも、この後もすっごいいろんな人たちがいっぱい楽しいことするからさ！ぜひぜひ概要欄もいまチェックして、チケット買ってくださーい！よろしくお願いします！
But, but, but, after this, lots of amazing people are going to do so many fun things! So please check the description box right now and buy tickets! Thank you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
こっちの景色見に行くぞ！ほらほらほら！
We're going to go check out the scenery over there! Come on, come on!
かなたんはこれから何を歌うのでしょうか？楽しみですね！みんな楽しい人いっぱい盛り上げてね！
What will Kanatan sing next? I'm looking forward to it! Everyone, get hyped with all the fun performers!
というわけでじゃあ、我々はそろそろドロンして、次のお友達の曲をね、届けますか！はい！
So with that, we'll be disappearing soon and delivering the song of our next friends! Yes!
じゃあ、締めのアレはいつものあれで！いつものあれ？あれじゃなくて！
Then, for the closing, let's do the usual thing! The usual thing? Not that one!
じゃあ行きます！せーの！ Color Rise Harmony!
Then here we go! Ready, go! Color Rise Harmony!
harmony 重ねた言葉 届け
harmony, layered words, reach out
たどたどしく 描いては ぎこちない と 笑ってた
clumsily drawing our dreams, laughing at how awkward they seemed
未来予想 あの日の続きを見よう
let’s continue the story we envisioned that day
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.